ANASTASIIA IVANCHENKO



+37061198239

in www.linkedin.com/in/a-ivanchenko



a.ivanchenko.eu@gmail.com

https://github.com/aivanchenk

ABOUT ME

Motivated and dedicated Front End Developer with a year of hands-on experience in creating, maintaining, and delivering new product features. Aiming to excel in front-end development to create meaningful changes for the end-user experience.

Devoted to project success by active task ownership, working together with multi-functional teams and soliciting feedback for continuous improvement. Demonstrated my learnig skills through moving twice to different countries adapting to new environment and learning new languages in a short amount of time.

EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

Part time job in UAB "Kompiuterizuoti sprendimai"

December 2023 - Current

- · Evaluated and integrated front-end tools, libraries, and frameworks according to project requirements and scalability, resulting in increased development efficiency.
- · Collaborated with cross-functional teams, including Backend developers and project managers, to ensure project objectives were accurately met.
- · Enhanced codebase efficiency, reducing redundancies and streamlining processes, resulting in a 20% resource optimization.
- · Adopted responsive web design principles for seamless user experiences across devices and browsers, prioritizing cross-browser compatibility.
- Improved platform usability with user-centric enhancements, contributing to a 30% enhancement in user satisfaction.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Part time project in Partisaner

September 2023 - January 2024

- Developed and maintained the front-end of a customer-facing e-commerce website.
- Component based website design design principles using React to create a dynamic and scalable website architecture
- Utilized ASP.NET to create MVC architecture of the project
- Conducted regular code reviews and provided mentorship to junior developers
- · Spearhead project planning and task management initiatives within the development team setting clear objectives, and delegating responsibilities

CERTIFICATES

November 2023

Advanced React by Meta

- Unit Testing, integration of React libraries
- TypeScript for type-safe React applications

EDUCATION

2022 - Current year

2021 - 2023

BACHELOR IN INFORMATICS

Kaunas University of Technology (Lithuania)

BACHELOR IN SOFTWARE ENGINEERING Kyiv National University of Trade and Economics

SKILLS

Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Ajax, React, TypeScript, SASS/SCSS

Other: Version Control Systems, Agile Development Process, Cross-browser

Compatibility, Responsive Design and Consistency, UI/UX Principles